<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<STORY id="mission-2" type="mission" number="2" dependencies="spaceship">
    <QUEST id="go-to-class">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="hallway" skin="normal">
                <SEQUENCE displayOnce="true">
                    <NARRATION>
                        As you walked along the hallway, you hear an announcement on the speakers. "Attention all cadets! The class Aesthetic Uses of Source 101 will begin in 5 minutes! Please proceed immediately to the designated classroom."
                    </NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you" expression="shocked">
                            What?! 5 minutes? I don’t even know where that is!
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>
                        "Latecomers will receive detention."
                    </NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">
                            Oh man, I have to get going!
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                </SEQUENCE>
                <COMPLETE_QUEST>go-to-class</COMPLETE_QUEST>
                <UNLOCK_QUEST>aesthetics-101</UNLOCK_QUEST>
            </LOCATION>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
    </QUEST>
    <QUEST id="aesthetics-101">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="classroom" skin="classOn">
                <SEQUENCE displayOnce="true">
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">Whew… Made it in time, somehow. But this classroom… what’s going on?</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <POPUP>
                        <IMAGE>messyClassroom.png</IMAGE>
                        <NARRATION>Bits and pieces of twine, cloth, thread and wool are strewn across the classroom tables. The other students are looking at the items nervously, unsure what to expect.</NARRATION>
                    </POPUP>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">This place is a mess! Are they sure this isn’t some sort of underwater basket weaving class?!</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>Before you can inspect anything further, someone walks up to you from behind.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>His towering presence is unmistakable – this is Professor Hartin Menz, a Grandmaster of the Academy. You even recognize his voice from the holographic brochures and promotional videos you’ve been perusing.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>But more than that, he is a member of the prestigious Crystal Order, an elite team of Sourcerers who uphold justice in the universe through their mastery of the Source.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>As you’ve heard, he and the other Grandmaster Lok-Kim, are in charge of research and education pertaining to the Source and its uses.</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Ah, our final student is here. And just in time, too!</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Let’s begin, then.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Today, you will learn to use the Source to manipulate these fabrics into a beautiful patchwork quilt.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">These are all basic techniques you’ll need to learn as a Sourcerer before we can go into more difficult stuff.</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <POPUP>
                        <IMAGE>patterns.png</IMAGE>
                        <NARRATION>Here are some of the patterns you’ll be using.</NARRATION>
                    </POPUP>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Now, try it out yourself!</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">This doesn't look so hard.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">Time to give it a shot!</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <PAUSE>
                        <OBJECT name="classHolo" skin="runicCarpet" x="709" y="144">
                            <CONTINUE></CONTINUE>
                        </OBJECT>
                    </PAUSE>
                </SEQUENCE>
                <OBJECT name="classHolo" skin="runicCarpet" x="709" y="144"></OBJECT>
                <OBJECT name="hartin-menz" skin="classroom" x="184" y="234"></OBJECT>
            </LOCATION>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
        <EXTERNAL_ACTION name="startMission">
            <ARGUMENT>2</ARGUMENT>
        </EXTERNAL_ACTION>
    </QUEST>
    <QUEST id="aesthetics-101-completed">
        <EFFECT></EFFECT>
        <SEQUENCE>
            <LOCATION name="classroom" skin="classOn"></LOCATION>
            <DIALOGUE>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">Excellent work, class! Some of these quilts are brilliant!</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">As for the rest… Hmm… I guess that’s why this isn’t art school!</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">That was harder than I thought it’d be… But at least I made it!</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">That’s all for today, class. You have a short break before your next class starts!</SPEECH>
            </DIALOGUE>
        </SEQUENCE>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>aesthetics-101</COMPLETE_QUEST>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>aesthetics-101-completed</COMPLETE_QUEST>
    </QUEST>
</STORY>