<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<STORY id="mission-21" type="mission" number="21" dependencies="spaceship">
    <QUEST id="force-calculus">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="yourRoom" skin="dim">
                <SEQUENCE>
                    <NARRATION>You woke up to Beat jumping up and down on your bed, and by extension, on you.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>Having stayed up late reading up on the intricacies of Streams Manipulation, you didn’t much appreciate the rude awakening.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>You sat up in your bed and brushed Beat aside grumpily.</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">What?</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="beat" expression="normal">Pixel sent me to come get you. She says you’re gonna be late for class if you don’t get your sleepy head out of bed soon.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">Oh, shucks! What time is it?</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="beat" expression="normal">You have exactly 4.75 minutes.</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>You hastily get dressed and rush off to the classroom.</NARRATION>
                </SEQUENCE>
            </LOCATION>
            <LOCATION name="classroom" skin="classOn">
                <SEQUENCE>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">I see some of you have been up late perusing the new material found on the Death Star.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">This level of dedication is inspiring indeed!</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">I have a feeling that some of you Cadets will be leading at the forefront of the battle against the Rogue Grandmaster in the years to come.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Today, I will be showing you how streams can be used in other ways as well.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Those with expert mastery of streams will have the capacity to become truly versatile Sourcerers in his or her own right, being able to adapt to all kinds of situations.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Now, let's begin!</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                </SEQUENCE>
                <OBJECT name="hartin-menz" skin="classroom" x="184" y="234"></OBJECT>
            </LOCATION>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
        <EXTERNAL_ACTION name="startMission">
            <ARGUMENT>21</ARGUMENT>
        </EXTERNAL_ACTION>
    </QUEST>
    <QUEST id="force-calculus-completed">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="classroom" skin="classOn">
                <SEQUENCE>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="normal">Well, that’s all for today folks! You are well on your way to becoming fully fledged Sorcerers!</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>You feel an immense sense of achievement completing this lesson’s tasks. Even Grandmaster Hartin seems proud of you and your fellow Cadets.</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="pixel" expression="excited">This is incredible! Think of all the things we can do with this knowledge in the future.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">Yeah, I know right. It’s pretty mind blowing. I finally feel like I’m on my way to becoming a skilled Sourcerer, maybe even skilled enough to be a Steward in the near future.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="pixel" expression="excited">Haha, well, let’s not get too carried away just yet. We still have much to learn.</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                </SEQUENCE>
            </LOCATION>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>force-calculus</COMPLETE_QUEST>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>force-calculus-completed</COMPLETE_QUEST>
    </QUEST>
</STORY>
           