<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<STORY id="mission-3" type="mission" number="3" dependencies="spaceship">
    <QUEST id="intro-to-ship-functions" helptext="Go to command center">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="hallway" skin="normal">
                <SEQUENCE displayOnce="true">
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">Hmm, the notification I got said that the next class will be in the Command Center.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">It should be somewhere along this corridor...</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                </SEQUENCE>
            </LOCATION>
             <LOCATION name="cmdCenter" skin="normal">
                <SEQUENCE displayOnce="true">
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">Ah, here it is!</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>The one leading the class this time round is a Steward, an assistant to the Master Sourcerers Hartin-Menz and Lok-Kim. He also happens to be in charge of navigation on the ship.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>Not long ago, he was a student of the Academy, just like you.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>In this class, you learn more about the Source Academy, a massive space station that also functions as a ship.</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="navigator" expression="bored">So, if you all did your research, you should know that the Grandmasters chose to settle in the Kepler-62 system because the planets nearby are one of the few that possess the Source in solid form – Source Crystals, after which the Crystal Order is named.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="navigator" expression="bored">The Academy conducts manned missions to the nearby planets to harvest these Crystals for research as well as search for life on them.</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="pixel" expression="thinking" audience="navigator">But sir, don’t we have functioning life-detection scanners?</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="navigator" expression="annoyed" audience="pixel">Every year, I get asked the same question...
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="navigator" expression="bored" audience="pixel">
                            Yes, we do. And obviously we would have used them if that were an option, but the sheer power of these raw Source Crystals block out many of our instruments. Which is a total pain in our posterior, but there isnt' really anything we can do about it.
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>
                        Pixel nudges you with her elbow.
                    </NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="pixel" expression="unimpressed">
                            Is he always like that?
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>You shrugged.</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">I heard the cadets have a nickname for him. Navigator "Grouch".</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>The two of you start to snicker uncontrollably. The navigator shoots you a death glare.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>You immediately stop and try to pull on a straight face. Struggling with every fibre of your being to not burst out in laughter.</NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>
                    After several more less interesting classes, the day ends.
                    </NARRATION>
                    <LOCATION name="yourRoom" skin="normal"></LOCATION>
                    <NARRATION>
                    You collapse on your bed, exhausted.
                    </NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">
                            This is all so much to take in.
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">
                            I wonder if I’ll ever get used to life like this? All the students and Stewards here look so busy and hardworking.
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">
                            Who knows? Maybe one day I’ll be a Steward too!
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">
                            Maybe even a Master?
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">...</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">
                            Guess I should go to sleep before I get too carried away.
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>
                        Instead of birds chirping outside your window, you wake to the sound of a blaring alarm from your academy-issued wrist device.
                    </NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">What is that racket?</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>
                        A message flashes across the screen: "CLASS IN 10 MINUTES."
                    </NARRATION>
                    <NARRATION>"Latecomers will receive detention."</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">10 minutes?! I gotta rush!</SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">It’s Aesthetics 101 again, so I have to head to the same classroom as yesterday...</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                </SEQUENCE>
                <COMPLETE_QUEST>intro-to-ship-functions</COMPLETE_QUEST>
                <UNLOCK_QUEST>aesthetics-101-again</UNLOCK_QUEST>
            </LOCATION>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
    </QUEST>
    <QUEST id="aesthetics-101-again" helptext="Go to classroom">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="classroom" skin="classOn">
                <SEQUENCE displayOnce="true">
                    <POPUP>
                        <IMAGE>messyClassroom-rocks.png</IMAGE>
                        <NARRATION>The state of the classroom is significantly different from yesterday. Instead of string and cloth, the room is littered with chunks of rock, granite, even marble.</NARRATION>
                    </POPUP>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">
                            Ah, the final member of our class is here. Let's begin today's lesson.
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">
                            Since yesterday went so smoothly, we can go a little faster today, I presume?
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>
                        Some of the students groan. You feel like joining them.
                    </NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz">
                            Last week you all tried your hand at using the Source to weave flat, 2D panels of cloth together.
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz">
                            Today, we’ll learn how to manipulate much heavier material into 3D sculptures!
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz">
                            It’s not as hard as it sounds. Most of the techniques involved, you already know from the last class.
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz">
                            Everyone, get to your desks!
                        </SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                    <NARRATION>You move to your assigned spot.</NARRATION>
                    <DIALOGUE>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">
                            All right, now use the Source to pick up a chunk of material. Doesn’t matter what.
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz" expression="happy">
                            We encourage creativity in this class!
                        </SPEECH>
                        <SPEECH speaker="you">I guess I’ll try…</SPEECH>
                    </DIALOGUE>
                </SEQUENCE>
                <EXTERNAL_ACTION name="startMission">
                    <ARGUMENT>3</ARGUMENT>
                </EXTERNAL_ACTION>
                <OBJECT name="hartin-menz" skin="classroom" x="184" y="234"></OBJECT>
            </LOCATION>
            <UNLOCK_QUEST>aesthetics-101-again-completed</UNLOCK_QUEST>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
    </QUEST>
    <QUEST id="aesthetics-101-again-completed">
        <EFFECTS></EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE>
            <LOCATION name="classroom" skin="classOn"></LOCATION>
            <NARRATION>Several hours later, the classroom tables are spick and span.</NARRATION>
            <NARRATION>In front of every student stands a solid statue of their own creation, some of them exact copies of ancient Greek masterpieces, while others are more abstract, modern works.</NARRATION>
            <DIALOGUE>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">I finally finished!</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin-menz">Well done, class. That's all for today.</SPEECH>
            </DIALOGUE>
            <NARRATION>The rest of the students split off for their next classes.</NARRATION>
            <NARRATION>You check your timetable.</NARRATION>
            <DIALOGUE>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">Looks like the next class is Wave Reading 101. What does that mean? Don’t tell me we’re… surfing?</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">Hmm, whatever it is, I still have some time before it starts. I guess I don't have to worry about it just yet.</SPEECH>
            </DIALOGUE>
        </SEQUENCE>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>aesthetics-101-again-completed</COMPLETE_QUEST>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>aesthetics-101-again</COMPLETE_QUEST>
    </QUEST>
</STORY>
