<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<STORY id="sidequest-19.1" type="sidequest" number="19.1" dependencies="spaceship">
    <QUEST id="find-sidequest-19.1">
        <EFFECTS>
            <LOCATION name="greatHall" skin="normal">
                <OBJECT name="trayOfFood" skin="normal" x="???" y="???">
                    <UNLOCK_QUEST>multiple-headaches</UNLOCK_QUEST>
                    <COMPLETE_QUEST>find-sidequest-19.1</COMPLETE_QUEST>
                </OBJECT>
            </LOCATION>
        </EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE></SEQUENCE>
    </QUEST>
    <QUEST id="multiple-headaches">
        <EFFECTS></EFFECTS>
        <SEQUENCE>
            <NARRATION>In the middle of an uncharacteristically silent dinner, the center stage lights up and projects a larger than life hologram of Grandmaster Hartin, who has a somber expression on his face.</NARRATION>
            <DIALOGUE>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin" expression="worried">Cadets – I regret to inform you that the Rogue Grandmaster has begun his assault on some of our reconnaissance vehicles.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin" expression="worried">As such, we will need to hasten our attack on the Deathcube.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin" expression="worried">As [TA name] has taught many of you in his Object Simulation class, we will need to design simulations of the interior of that ship in order to carry out a successful mission.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin" expression="worried">We want to harness the power of having a large amount of Cadets – and very intelligent ones, I may add – to find the best possible course of action in this scenario.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin" expression="worried">Whoever comes up with the best working assault pattern, will have their design used during our real assault.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="hartin" expression="worried">This is serious, Cadets. We need all the help you can provide.</SPEECH>
            </DIALOGUE>
            <NARRATION>With that, the hologram disappeared.</NARRATION>
            <DIALOGUE>
                <SPEECH speaker="pixel" expression="surprised">...Wow.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">Sounds like they're putting a lot of faith in us.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">We can't let them down!</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="pixel">Yeah.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="pixel">Come on! Let's quickly head to the classroom after this to start working on the problem.</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="pixel">Who knows, they might even choose one of ours!</SPEECH>
                <SPEECH speaker="you">Then we should put in our best effort!</SPEECH>
            </DIALOGUE>
            <NARRATION>The two of you swiftly finish your meal and hurry down to the classrooms, already thinking of what you might put in your simulations...</NARRATION>
        </SEQUENCE>
        <COMPLETE_QUEST>multiple-headaches</COMPLETE_QUEST>
        <EXTERNAL_ACTION name="startMission">
            <ARGUMENT>19.1</ARGUMENT>
        </EXTERNAL_ACTION>
    </QUEST>
</STORY>
